jobmob.co.il 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy | JobMob

This privacy policy covers all of the Share Select Media websites (“SSM Sites”), including JobMob, and related content. Please read this statement before using this or any of the SSM Sites. Your use of these sites indicates your agreement to abide by the terms stated herein.

### Who we are

Our website address is: https://jobmob.co.il/

### What personal data we collect and why we collect it

Except where exceptionally indicated, Share Select Media (“SSM”) is the sole owner of the information collected on SSM Sites via the following mechanisms:

**Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.  We will not pass this information on to any other organization.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

**Cookies**

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

**Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**Log Files**

Activity on all SSM sites is recorded in standard web server log files. These files store information about each visit such as but not limited to the visitor’s IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), pages viewed e.g. on entry/exit, platform type, and visit date/time. This information is used for SSM’s understanding of user behavior in order to improve the user experience. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Analytics**

Activity on all SSM sites is also recorded using [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/) and [Matomo Analytics](https://matomo.org/).

Google Analytics' privacy policy is part of Google's here: https://policies.google.com/privacy. You may opt out of Google Analytics' browser tracking by using one of the freely available browser plugins for that.

Matomo's privacy policy is at https://matomo.org/privacy-policy/. You may opt out of Matomo's tracking by enabling your browser's ‘Do Not Track' feature if your browser has one.

**Outbound Links**

The SSM Sites will contain links to other sites. Some of the clicks to those sites are recorded in our database, although they are not linked to any personally identifiable information. Also, some of these links may be affiliate links. Please be aware that SSM is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites, and as such, users should be careful to search out and read the privacy policies of each and every linked Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy only applies to information collected by Share Select Media.

### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website, we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Additional information

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Share Select Media may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on any of the SSM Sites.

**Business Transitions**  
If Share Select Media undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will likely be part of the assets transferred.

**Notification of Changes**  
In the event of changes to this privacy policy, Share Select Media promises to inform our readers of such changes via blog posts, direct email or whatever communication method deemed best. It is important for us to keep our users abreast of the information we gather and how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we may be required to disclose it.

**Contact Us**  
We at Share Select Media are always eager to hear from our users. To reach us if you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, email privacy AT shareselectmedia DOT com.  Share Select Media uses the submitted email address solely for the purpose of corresponding with our users, and will not pass this information on to any other organization without our users’ express written consent.

**Last update**

May 28, 2019
